Hello Sanjeev ji, good day, let me tell you
where are you tracking the momentum, if you are here today, then
see the Mama entry numbers are very
good, so short term money has moved into that, but I am still
thinking Bank
Sargam Russia, I will give you 37,000, whatever you say, Bank
Nifty is going to come, whether it comes in 15 days or
a month, but there are students in the bank and a lot
in the media department, the
commentary that has come today from Bandhan Bank and Mirchi Matar
Microfinance, they say that landing is
dam recovery 125 per cent and September
tweet 98% management right now, please recommend
Vandana etc. and make it public in Avery, you will be
recorded midcap bank, let me give
you an update of Rubaru Circle, I had given you 9350 anti
finance earlier, it went to 95.50,
book profit in that and but now there are two pieces of ₹2 handsome,
here I should also tell that the
tube bank of 1035, I gave a wire of 1150, it has become
1185, which is probably the micro
finance law and urban bank class dress
Teamly value today's two picks if you say
I will start with the phone ji machine, tell the
lips, the first one will be ICICI Lombard
Insurance from the ground and Insurance Guddu
Yadav stream ICICI Lombard after getting
1658 character 215 346 take it in 1540
stoploss is 1510 12 this is going back to see a little
Bahubali my favorite
updates UP Bank of Baroda Bank of
Baroda will give the highest record profit in this quarter
which is your July deal because
of health take it in eighty-four and a half that bus
stop love 7250 decided to ₹90 then
ambulance packing machine on long reference from Bank of Baroda
clear you today's hot topic of
discussion is that
what is the reward of the IPO of matches, should we invest money in
7276, see this in its price point,
every caution, whatever trend is there, it is
telling this friends and friends let's everyone see
this parking rate price up  Fiction
but this talk will make money over the next few
years to figure out where the winds
and used to give you are you written with this
business news no brainer however as I told
you there is no metric of its valuation
before so it
is difficult for us to comment but I think you must be seen in
your portfolio in small quantities on this
very measured opinion Machine snake
seems to be taking Lal's opinion right now and on midcap IT, is there
any special reason why you are
seeing such tremendous momentum in midcap IT
I distributed my sweets so they were ruling Russia's
entry into the army, we have gone from a very low right now
I think should I go into
National Tech, Tech Mahindra will give you are right but how can I am
by
students Dabi Yadav Banking stocks,
if Bank of Baroda is 140 then I will pay
attention to that or RBL I
see 400 or 350 and so I am
hopeful, I am very bullish on banks
and this is the only option but I like it midcap IT  Has been a very very bright
performer however
most validation drink settings
ball real again will commit midcap bank
listen so midcap bank management bank of
baroda and machine on bell sir have been watching you for a long time
giving a pistol and technical call also